<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Adventures with Adonai</title>
    <link href="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai" />
    <updated>2026-01-13T17:57:21+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Arianna Mulligan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Where it all started...</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arianna Mulligan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/a-story-leading-up-to-my-present-day.html"/>
        <id>https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/a-story-leading-up-to-my-present-day.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/IMG_9543.jpeg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Newsletters"/>

        <updated>2026-01-13T17:42:33+01:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/IMG_9543.jpeg" alt="pretty Queenstown, NZ" />
                    A short testimony The Lord put me in a Christian family through his mercy. I loved Jesus, but when I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/IMG_9543.jpeg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="pretty Queenstown, NZ" /></p>
                
    <h2 id="a-short-testimony">
      A short testimony
    </h2>

  <p>
    The Lord put me in a Christian family through his mercy.
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>For the Lord is good and his love endures forever;<br>    his faithfulness continues through all generations.<br></blockquote>
      <figcaption>Psalm 100:5 NIV</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    I loved Jesus, but when I got into high school and then university, I slowly began putting people above God. Jesus became my friend, not my Lord. Because of that, I found myself living two lives: one of partying and chasing the approval of others, and another of church on a Sunday—if I didn’t have anything else on.<br><br>Sometimes, in the middle of a party, I’d step outside and think, <em>What am I doing this for? What’s the point of this? What’s the point of life?</em> And instead of sitting with those questions, I’d fill my mind (and my stomach) with meaningless things just to forget the reality of what I was doing.<br><br>This back-and-forth went on for a few years. <em>Yes, I love Jesus! Yes, I love partying!</em>&nbsp; But through Jesus, his forgiveness—and through so many small Christian groups, clubs, and loyal friendships—I slowly started making decisions that put God above people. Gods mercy is so good!&nbsp;
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>Show me your ways, Lord, teach me your paths.<br>Guide me in your truth and teach me, for you are God my Saviour, <br>and my hope is in you all day long.<br>Remember, Lord, your great mercy and love, for they are from of old.<br>Do not remember the sins of my youth and my rebellious ways; <br>according to your love remember me, <br>for you, Lord, are good.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Psalm 25:4-7 NIV (the whole chapter is awesome)</figcaption>
    </figure>

    <h2 id="why-a-missionary">
      Why a missionary?
    </h2>

  <p>
    When I truly found Jesus again—and actually wanted to give Him my degree, my job, my life, and the people I surrounded myself with—that’s when my faith stopped being just a belief and started becoming faith in action.<br><br>Reading the Bible no longer felt like a podcast I’d listen to and forget an hour later. I read it and wanted to live it. I just didn't know how. So when I read,
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>Religion that God our Father accepts as pure and faultless is this: to look after orphans and widows in their distress and to keep oneself from being polluted by the world.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>James 1:27 (NIV)</figcaption>
    </figure>

  <p>
    my response was basically, <em>Okay God!! Please help me to do this, in one way, shape, or form!</em><br><br>During this time, I was deeply encouraged by testimonies at church, and I wanted more. One day, while looking through my grandma’s bookcase, I found <a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/261391.Visions_Beyond_the_Veil" target="_blank">Visions Beyond the Veil</a>. I devoured it—through a lot of tears—and told God, “<em>I want this to be my life.</em>” After that, I searched up the author, which led me to Iris Global. I joined one of their online mission schools, and found hearts burning with the same love for Jesus and missions.<br><br>After finishing my Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, I moved back in with my parents for a few months to “check” whether God wanted me to use my degree in a normal 9–5 job (to earn money and <i>then</i> go). I applied for countless internships and graduate roles in New Zealand and Denmark. At the same time, I prayed and asked God whether I should stay in New Zealand or go to my mum’s country—my first country—Denmark, to reconnect with family and relearn the language.<br><br>God answered very clearly: every single job application in New Zealand was rejected… and He provided a flight to Denmark.<br><br>This timing was incredible because I had also applied for the Iris Portugal Harvest School. I spent most of 2025 in Denmark, God gave me a summer cleaning job there to help pay for Harvest School, and He even provided me a remote job so I could travel without constantly stressing about finances. Now, I only <i>sometimes</i> worry! Yay!<br><br>I love learning languages, and I love travelling. And I’ve realised that I want to do the travelling that only God wants me to do and with His people. Cool experiences mean nothing compared to knowing Jesus and growing closer to Him.
  </p>

  <p>
    Going on from that, the book of Philippians is awesome. Here's a verse that's always motivated me:
  </p>

    <figure class="blockquote">
      <blockquote>What is more, I consider everything a loss because of the surpassing worth of knowing Christ Jesus my Lord, for whose sake I have lost all things. I consider them garbage, that I may gain Christ and be found in him, not having a righteousness of my own that comes from the law, but that which is through faith in a Christ—the righteousness that comes from God on the basis of faith. I want to know Christ—yes, to know the power of his resurrection and participation in his sufferings, becoming like him in his death, and so, somehow, attaining to the resurrection from the dead.</blockquote>
      <figcaption>Philippians 3:8-11 (NIV)</figcaption>
    </figure>

    <h2 id="why-brazil">
      Why Brazil?
    </h2>

  <p>
    While I was doing my degree, I started Brazilian Jiu Jitsu and quickly realised how much I loved it. '<em>Doing Jiu Jitsu in it's original country would be awesome'</em>, I thought. When I later joined the Harvest School in Portugal, I loved learning Portuguese, and that curiosity for Brazil grew (they speak Portuguese there too, funnily enough). One night at the school, I brought this to God in prayer. I told Him how I felt… and ended it with, “God, I want Your will for my life, not mine.”<br><br>I hadn’t told anyone about this desire. Not a single person.<br><br>The very next day, during Sunday worship, a woman I had only spoken to once before came up to me and prophesied over me. And funnily enough, she said that I would speak several languages—and that I would go to Brazil. WHAT 😭<br><br>Later, when I shared this with the school, the Harvest School leader said he felt God had told him to give his Bible—printed side-by-side in English and Portuguese—to someone.<br><br>And now, here I am, reading it!!!!!&nbsp;
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/me-n-bible.png" height="3088" width="2316" alt="me n bible"  sizes="(min-width: 37.5em) 1600px, 80vw" srcset="https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/responsive/me-n-bible-xs.png 384w ,https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/responsive/me-n-bible-sm.png 600w ,https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/responsive/me-n-bible-md.png 768w ,https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/responsive/me-n-bible-lg.png 1200w ,https://arimulligan.github.io/adventureswithadonai/media/posts/3/responsive/me-n-bible-xl.png 1600w">
      
    </figure>

    <h2 id="now-what">
      Now what?
    </h2>

  <p>
    My current thoughts:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li>Visit Brazil and their Iris bases, and see which one God wants me in, if any.</li><li>Been thinking about end of February, or the start of March to visit.</li><li>I've been wondering if I book a one way ticket, or a return ticket...<br></li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    Thanks for reading so far &lt;3
  </p>

  <p>
    P.S. Let me know if any of you guys have anything I can pray for, and I would love prayer as well :)&nbsp;
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
